Himanshu Sharma

Backend Java Developer



- Mananshu241100@gmail.com
- **** 7906536070
- Pulandshahr, U.P, India
- https://github.com/himkrishna

Profile

A self-disciplined, hardworking, and passionate Backend Java Developer with proficiency in Java, SQL, Spring Boot, Data Structures and Algorithms. Problem-solving mindset and ability to perform well in team collaboration. Looking forward to utilizing my current skillset and experience of working on projects to create a mark in the software industry and achieve organizational goals.

Professional Experience

Management Trainee, HSIL Limited 06/2019 – 12/2019 | Gurugram, India Joined as Management trainee for Marketing and sales

Territory Manager, *Brilloca Limited formerly Known as HSIL Limited*01/2020 – 03/2022 | Bareilly, India
Work as a territory manager in the assigned territory to manage sales and marketing of the territory. and also manages a team of RSOs

Area Sales Manager, Hindware Limited formerly known as Brilloca Limited 04/2022 – 05/2022 | Bareilly, india Promoted as Area Sales Manager

Projects

India Today News Website - Clone

- India Today is a news website and it offers news on everything from business, finance, politics, science, and technology.
- Developed along with a team of 4 members in one week.
- We mainly worked on the front end of the website.
- My task in this collaborative project was to create the bottom part of the front page by using HTML and CSS.

Education

Full Stack Web Development, Masai School

04/2022 - present

Courses

- Web Development
- Data Structures and Algorithms
- Soft Skills

Bachelor of Technology (B. Tech.) in Civil

Engineering, GLA University

08/2015 - 05/2019 | Mathura, India

Intermediate CBSE Board,

Happy Blue Bird Public School 04/2013 – 05/2014

SSC CBSE BOARD,

Happy Blue Bird Public School 04/2011 – 05/2012

Skills

Java, Javascript, HTML, CSS, SQL, SpringBoot

Languages

English

• • • •

Hindi

• • • • •